When you train your neural network is
当你开始训练你的神经网络时，
important to initialize the weights
将权重参数初始化是非常
randomly. For logistic regression, it was
重要的。在逻辑回归的问题中，
okay to initialize the weights to zero,
把权重参数初始化成零是可行的，
but for a neural network of initialize
但把神经网络的权重参数
the weights the parameters to all zero in
全部初始化为零，并使用梯度下降，
an apply gradient descent, it won't work.
却无法获得预期的效果。
Let's see why. So you have here two input
让我们一起来深入探讨这个问题。这里有
features, so n0 is equal to two and two
两个输入样本参数，因此n0等于2，还有两个
hidden units, so n1 is equal to two. And
隐藏神经元，因此n1也等于2，
so the matrix associated with a hidden
所以与隐藏层关联的权重w1，
layer or w1 it is going to be 2x2. Let's
是一个2x2的矩阵。
say that you initialize it to all zeros
现在我们将这个矩阵的
0 0 0 0 2 by 2 matrix and let's say b1
初始值都设为0，同样我们将矩阵b1的值
is also equal to 0 0. Turns out
也都初始化为零。偏离度矩阵b1
initializing the bias terms B to 0 is
的初始值都是0，这并不会影响最终
actually okay, but the initializing W to
结果，但是将权重参数矩阵w1初始值都
all zeros is a problem. So the problem
设置为零，会引起某些问题。
with this formal initialization is that
这样的初始权重参数，会导致
for any example you give it, you have
无论使用什么样的样本进行训练，
that a 1 1 and a 1 2 will be equal. All
隐藏层中第一个神经元与第二个神经元始终是相同的。
right, so this activation and this
没错，这第一个神经元和这第二个神经元
activation would be same because both of
将是完全一致的，因为
these hidden units are computing exactly
这些隐藏神经元在进行完全相同
the same function, and then when you
的计算工作。当你进行
compute back propagation, it turns out
反向传播的计算时，由于对称问题，这些
that d z1 1 and d z1 2 will also be the
隐藏神经将会在同样的条件下被初始化，
same. Kind of by symmetry, right. Both of
最终会导致z[1]1的导数
these hidden units will initialize the
与z[1]2的导数也
same way. Technically for what I'm saying
相同。同样的，
I'm assuming that the outgoing weights
我可以假设输出的权重
are also identical. So that W 2 is equal
也是相同的，所以输出权重参数矩阵w2
to 0 0 but if you initialize the neural
也等于[0,0]，但如果你使用这种
network this way, then this hidden unit
方法来初始化神经网络，那么这个隐藏神经元(a[1]1)
and this hidden unit are completely
和这个隐藏神经元(a[1]2)也是
identical. So they're completely
完全相同的，它们实现的
sometimes you say they're completely
是完全相同的功能，有时候
symmetric which just means that the
我们也称这是
computing exactly the same function. And
“对称”的（重复的）。
by kind of a proof by induction it turns
我们来归纳一下这个结果，
out that after every single iteration of
经过每一次训练
training you've two hidden units are
迭代，你将会得到两个
still confusing exactly the same
实现完全相同功能
function.
的隐藏神经元。
Since part of the show that dW will be a
之前的部分视频中，W的导数将会是一个
matrix that looks like this, where every
矩阵，大概看上去是这样，每一行
row takes on the same value. So we
都是相同的，然后我们
perform a weight update, so you perform
进行一个权重更新，
when you perform a weight update, w1 gets
当你在实际操作时，
updated as w1 minus alpha times DW. You
w1将被更新成w1-α*dw，
find that w1 after every iteration will
而你将会发现，经过每一次迭代后，
have you know the first row equal to the
w1的第一行与第二行
second row. So it's possible to construct
是相同的。所以根据上述信息来归纳，
a proof by induction, that if you
我们可以得到一个证明结果，
initialize all the ways, all the values
如果你在神经网络中将所有权重参数矩阵w
of W to 0, then because both hidden units
的值初始化为零，由于两个隐藏神经元
start off computing the same function,
实现了相同的计算功能，
and both hidden units have the same
并且也将同样的影响
influence on the output unit, then after
作用在输出神经元上，经过
one iteration that same statement is
一次迭代后，依然会得到相同的结果。
still true, the two fields in units are
这两个神经元依然是“对称”
still symmetric and therefore by
的，同样推导下去，
induction after two iterations, three
经过两次迭代、三次迭代
iterations, and so on, no matter how long
以及更多次迭代，无论
you train in your network, both hidden
你将这个神经网络训练多久，
units are still computing exactly the
这两个隐藏神经元仍然在使用同样的功能
same function. And so in this case,
进行运算。在这个例子中，
there's really no point to having more
由于隐藏神经元实现的
than one hidden unit because they're all
都是相同的功能，
computing the same thing. And of course
所以我们使用一个就够了。
for larger neural networks, less you have
在更大的神经网络中，假设我们有
three features, and maybe a very large
三个输入特征值，以及非常多的
number of hidden units, a similar
隐藏神经元，一个类似的结论
argument works to show that what the new
也同样成立，就像
network like this because I won't drawn
我现在画的这样，我不会
all the edges. If you initialize the way
画出所有的连接线，如果你依然将权重参数矩阵
to zero then all of your hidden units
初始化为零，那么无论你运行
are symmetric and no matter how long you
梯度下降多长时间，
run gradient descent. They'll all
所有的隐藏神经元都将是“对称”的。它们
continue to compute exactly the same
依然将运行在完全相同
function. So that's not helpful because
的功能下，而这并不能给我们
you want two different hidden units to
任何帮助，因为我们希望两个不同的
compute different functions. The solution
隐藏神经元能实现不同的功能。因此
to this is to initialize your parameters
只有进行随机初始化能够解决这样
randomly. So here's what you do. You can
的问题。让我们看看如何在Python中操作。我们
set W 1 equals NP dot random dot R and n
通常使用w[1]=np.random.randn((2,2))*0.01
of this generates our Gaussian random
（randn会进行高斯随机分布）这样的写法
variable 2 2 and then usually you
来对这个2*2的矩阵进行随机初始化，
multiply this by a very small number
并乘上一个非常小的数，
such as 0.01. So you initialize it to
比如0.01。这样操作后，你已经将
very small random values and then b, emmmm
权重参数矩阵赋予了非常小的随机初始值，然后
it turns out that b does not have this
对于b来说，b并不会由于初始值为零而产生
symmetry problem what's called a
对称问题，
symmetry breaking problem.
或称之为对称失效问题，
So is okay to initialize b to just zeros.
所以使用b[i]=np.zeros((2,1))将b矩阵初始值设为零(这里应该是zeros，视频后面会补上)。
Because so long as W is initialized
好了，现在权重参数矩阵w已经使用了
randomly. You start off with the
随机初始化，不同的
different hidden units computing
隐藏神经元会承担不同的
different things and so you no longer
计算工作，我们也不会再遇到
have this emmm symmetry breaking problem.
类似前面说的对称失效问题了。
And then similarly for w2 you can
然后我们可以用同样的方法来
initialize that randomly and b2 you can
将w[2]进行随机初始化，b[2]也
initialize that to zero. So you might be
依然可以初始化为零。好了，现在
wondering you know where did this
你想知道的可能是
constant come from, and why is it 0.01?
为什么使用这个常量，并且为什么是0.01？
why not put the number 100 or 1000? Turns
为什么我们不把它设置为100或1000？主要
out that we usually prefer to initialize
原因是，我们通常比较喜欢使用
the ways to very very small random
非常非常小的随机
values, because emmm if you're using a
初始值，而当你使用一个
say tanh or sigmoid activation function
tanh或者sigmoid的激活函数时，
or if you have a sigmoid even just at
或者在输出层使用了
the output layer, if the waves are too
sigmoid函数，如果步长过大，
large then when you compute the
那么当你要计算
activation values remember that z1 is
激活值的时候，你应该还记得
equal to w1 X plus B and then on a 1 is
z[1]=w[1]*x+b[1]，
the activation function applied to z1. So
而a[1]=g[1](z[1])。所以，
if W is very big Z will be very big or
当w非常大的时候，z（的绝对值）也相应的会非常大，
these some values of Z will be either
或者说z可能是一个非常大的数，
very large or very small. And so in that
或者是一个非常小的数。在这样的
case you're more likely to end up at
情况下，你可能最终会
these flat parts of the tenh function or
发现图上tanh和sigmoid函数中
the sigmoid function where the slope of
这些相对平坦的部分，梯度的斜率（变化率）
the gradient is very small.
非常小。
Meaning that gradient descent would be
这意味着梯度下降
very slow and so learning would be very
会非常缓慢，所以整个学习过程也会变得
slow.
尤为缓慢。
So just a recap if W is too large you're
概括一下，如果w过大，你
more likely to end up even at the very
很容易在开始时就
start of training with very large values
得出一个非常大的
of Z, which causes your tanh and sigmoid
z，而这会导致你的tanh和sigmoid
activation function to be saturated on
激活函数学习进度缓慢，
the slowing down learning. If you don't
无法实现预期功能。如果在
have any sigmoid or tanh activation
你的神经网络中未使用
functions throughout your neural network,
任何sigmoid或者tanh激活函数，
this is less of an issue, but if you're
这种情况可能不明显，但是如果你
doing binary classification and your
使用二分类，并且你的输出神经元
output unit is a sigmoid function, then
使用了sigmoid函数，那么
you know you just don't want the initial
你不会希望初始
parameters to be too large. So that's why
参数过大。所以这就是
multiplying by 0.01 would be something
为什么我们说在上述公式中需要
reasonable to try or any other small
乘以0.01或者其他
number and same for w2
比较小的数值。同样，对权重参数矩阵w2
this can be a random randn I guess this
来说，我们可以表示成
would be 1 by 2 in this example times
w[2]=np.random.randn((1,2))*0.01
0.01. Zeros there. So finally it turns
噢上面应该是zeros。这里还有另外一个结论
out that sometimes they can be better
分享给大家，有时候会有比0.01更为合适的
constants than 0.01. When you're training
一些数值。当你在训练一个
a neural network with just one hidden
仅含一个隐藏层的神经网络时，
layer, this is a relatively shallow your
显而易见，0.01这个数值
network without too many hidden layers
在类似于这样不含过多隐藏层的
setting to 0.01 will probably work ok,
神经网络中是非常合适的，
but when you're training a very very
但当你要训练一个非常非常复杂
deep neural network, then you might want
的神经网络时，我们会使用
to pick a different constant in 0.001.
一个不同的数值，0.001.
And in next week's material we'll talk a
在下周的课程中我们会
little bit about how and when you might
简单说一下我们如何根据不同的情况，
want to choose a different constant than
来挑一个与0.01不同
0.01. But either way it will usually end
的数值。不论如何，通常情况
up being a relatively small number. So
我们的计算结果都会是一个相对小的数值。
that's it. So this week videos you now
所以这周我们就先讲到这里，从这期的教学视频中，
know how to set up a neural network of a
你应该学到了如何设计一个含有单独隐藏层
hidden layer initialize the parameters
的神经网络、参数初始化、
make predictions using forward prop as
使用正向传播进行预测
well as compute derivatives and it's in
以及在梯度下降时使用反向传播中涉及
gradient descent using back prop. So that
的导数计算。所以
you should be able to do the quizzes as
现在你应该能完成课后测试和
well as this week's program exercises. Best
本周的编程联系。祝
of luck with that. I hope you have fun
你好运。我希望各位能喜欢我的课程，
with my exercise and look forward to
在其中学到知识，也希望
seeing you in two weeks cool materials.
在后几期课程中能继续见到各位。